Finding Aid for University of Michigan Class Albums
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- 1868 Class Album
  - Students
    - Kinne, L.G. '68 (Box 9)
    - McReynolds, L.E. '68 (Box 9)
    - Williams, O.F. '69 (Box 9)
    - Waterbury, Charles (Box 9)
  - Others
    - Englick (?), '67 (Box 9)
    - Taylor, '67 (Box 9)
    - Elwood '67 (Box 9)
    - Hall, James W. '67-68 (Box 9)
    - Vreeland '69 (Box 9)
    - Gibson, '69 (Box 9)
    - Chaney '69 (Box 9)
    - Woodworth '69 (Box 9)
    - Hamilton '69 (Box 9)
    - Perry '69 (Box 9)
    - Hall '69 (Box 9)
    - Guthrie '69 (Box 9)
    - Fleming '70 (Box 9)
    - Lovell '70 (Box 9)
    - Milner '72 (Box 9)
    - Niatrice (?) '72 (Box 9)
    - Williams '67-'68 (Box 9)
    - Bassett, C.C. (Box 9)
    - Hughers, J.S (Box 9)
      [115]
    - Howe, R. L.; '65 (Box 9)
    - Atwater, Amzi (Box 9)
      [124]
    - Bates, George, '70 (?) (Box 9)
    - Cotton, J.H. (Box 9)
      [136]
    - Burgess, O.A. (Box 9)
      [143]
    - Eriett, Isaac (Box 9)
      [144]
    - Franklin, Benjamin (Box 9)
      [142]
    - Baxter, William (Box 9)
      [145]
    - Pinkerton, L.L. (Box 9)
      [146]
    - Burnet, D.S. (Box 9)
    - Milligan, President of KY University (Box 9)
    - Shephard, S.E. (Box 9)
      [151]
    - Henderson, D.T. (Box 9)
    - Mrs. M.M. Goodwin (Box 9)
      [152]
    - a number of photos of individuals are not identified (Box 9)
  - NWC University
    - Benton, A.R Pres. N.W.C. University) (Box 9)
      [103]
    - Houshour, S.K. (Box 9)
      [7104]
    - Brown, R.L. (Box 9)
      [107]
    - Dowling, W.W. (Box 9)
      [108]
- 1868 Class Album (J. C. Reynolds)
  - Faculty
    - Adams, Charles K. (Box 10)
    - Angell, James (Box 10)
    - Boise, J. R. (Box 10)
    - Chapin, Lucius D. (Box 10)
    - Curtis, Allen J. (Box 10)
    - Davis, J. B. (Box 10)
    - Douglass, Silas H. (Box 10)
    - Frieze, Henry (Box 10)
    - Haven, Erastus O. (Box 10)
    - Olney, Edward (Box 10)
    - Palmer, Alonzo B. (Box 10)
    - Prescott, Albert B. (Box 10)
    - Robinson, Stillman W. (Box 10)
    - Spence, Adam K. (Box 10)
    - Tappan, Henry (Box 10)
    - TenBrook, Andrew (Box 10)
    - Williams, G. P. (Box 10)
    - Winchell, Alexander (Box 10)
    - Wood, DeVolson (Box 10)
  - Students
    - Anderson, W. K. (Box 10)
    - Bain, P. M. (Box 10)
    - Beazell, J. S. (Box 10)
    - Belville, W. W. (Box 10)
    - Betts, L. B. (Box 10)
    - Blackburn, F. A. (Box 10)
    - Boardman, W. H. (Box 10)
    - Brainard, F. A. (Box 10)
    - Burns, E. C. (Box 10)
    - Butler, Billy (Box 10)
    - Carter, A. (Box 10)
    - Chafee, R. R. (Box 10)
    - Chapin, J. H. (Box 10)
    - Clay, B. J. (Box 10)
    - Cocker, W. J. (Box 10)
      [139]
    - Coffey, J. C. (Box 10)
    - Crouse, D. W. (Box 10)
    - Davis, J. J. (Box 10)
    - Dean, O. H. (Box 10)
    - Demmon, I. N. (Box 10)
    - Dewey, R. S. (Box 10)
    - Durkee, H. R. (Box 10)
    - Entrekin, T. (Box 10)
    - Evans, E. P. (Box 10)
    - Freeman, J. C. (Box 10)
    - Fry, G. C. (Box 10)
    - Gale, E. W. (Box 10)
    - Harrington, M. W. (Box 10)
    - Havens, M. K. (Box 10)
    - Heldenbrand, A. H. (Box 10)
      [135]
    - Hessenmueller, E. L. (Box 10)
    - Hickey, G. S. (Box 10)
    - House, J. H. (Box 10)
    - Jenison, E. S. (Box 10)
    - Jenne, R. N. (Box 10)
    - Jewett, H. S. (Box 10)
    - Johnston, E. S. (Box 10)
    - Kendall, J. L. (Box 10)
    - Kinne, L. G. (Box 10)
    - Kinsley, W. A. (Box 10)
    - Lord, H. W. (Box 10)
    - Lovell, E. C. (Box 10)
    - Lyman, F. H. (Box 10)
    - Mack, A. J. (Box 10)
    - Magill, J. C. (Box 10)
    - Maok, A. J. (Box 10)
    - McHarg, W. S. (Box 10)
    - McReynolds, L. E. (Box 10)
    - Miller, H. H. C. (Box 10)
    - Morrill, F. F. (Box 10)
      [116]
    - Pattengill, A. H. (Box 10)
    - Pennell, G. (Box 10)
    - Perkins, W. R. (Box 10)
    - Philbrick, P. H. (Box 10)
    - Poor, C. (Box 10)
    - Reeves, R. J. (Box 10)
    - Shaw, T. M. (Box 10)
    - Smith, F. M. (Box 10)
    - Steere, J. B. (Box 10)
    - Storey, R. C. (Box 10)
    - Stuart, W. J. (Box 10)
    - Tallman, E. H. (Box 10)
    - Tarlton, L. P. (Box 10)
    - Walter, E. L. (Box 10)
    - Waterbury, Charles F. (Box 10)
      [169]
    - Wells, M. N. (Box 10)
      [100]
    - Whiffen, J. W. (Box 10)
      [156]
    - Williams, B. (Box 10)
      [134]
    - Williams, C. F. (Box 10)
      [168]
    - Wilson, A. (Box 10)
      [123]
  - Buildings and Miscellaneous
    - Alpha Delta (Box 10)
    - Apollo Belvedere (Box 10)
    - Chemical laboratory (Box 10)
    - Chi Psi (Box 10)
    - Civil Engineers of '68 (Box 10)
    - Class of '67 composite (Box 10)
    - Class of '69 composite (Box 10)
    - Class of '70, Cornell University (Box 10)
    - Delta Phi (Box 10)
    - Jimmie (Box 10)
    - Laocoon and his two sons (Box 10)
    - Medical Building (Box 10)
    - Medical Building (Box 10)
    - Nydia (Box 10)
    - Nydia (Box 10)
    - Observatory (Box 10)
    - Observatory (Box 10)
    - Owls of '68 (Box 10)
    - Phi Delta Theta (Box 10)
    - Robert (Box 10)
    - Scientifics of '68 (Box 10)
    - Storr's School House, Atlanta Georgia (Box 10)
    - University buildings (Box 10)
    - University buildings (Box 10)
    - University Hall (Box 10)
- 1868 Class Album (Box 10)
  (Daniel Webster Crouse album)
  - Class Album 1868 (Box 10A)
    (with exception of pictures of Crouse and some family members, photos are not identified)
- 1869 Class Album (Box 10A)
  (William Corwin Johns album)
  - Faculty
    - Adams, [A]. Charles Kendall (Box 11)
    - Boise, James Robinson (Box 11)
    - Campbell, James Valentine (Box 11)
    - Chapin, Rev. Lucius Delison (Box 11)
    - Cooley, Thomas McIntyre (Box 11)
    - Curtis, Allen Jeremiah (Box 11)
    - D'Ooge, Rev. Martin Luther (Box 11)
    - Douglas, Silas Hamilton (Box 11)
    - Evans, Edward Payson (Box 11)
    - Frieze, Henry Simmons (Box 11)
    - Haven, Rev. Erastus Otis (Box 11)
    - Merriman, George Benjamin (Box 11)
    - Olney, Edward (Box 11)
    - Palmer, Alonzo Benjamin (Box 11)
    - Robinson, Stillman Williams (Box 11)
    - Spence, Adam Knight (Box 11)
    - Ten Brook, Rev. Andrew (Box 11)
    - Tyler, Moses Coit (Box 11)
    - Walker, Charles Irish (Box 11)
    - Walter, Edward Lorraine (Box 11)
    - Watson, James Craig (Box 11)
    - Williams, Rev. George Palmer (Box 11)
    - Winchell, Alexander (Box 11)
    - Wood, DeVolson (Box 11)
  - Students
    - Alexander, Hugh Byron (Box 11)
    - Bancroft, Coleman (Box 11)
    - Beatty, Charles Tupper (Box 11)
    - Becker, Frederick Walter (Box 11)
    - Bradley, Franklin (Box 11)
    - Brownsberger, Sidney (Box 11)
    - Brush, Charles Francis (Box 11)
    - Butler, William Addison (Box 11)
      [33, 81, 82]
    - Campbell, Oscar James (Box 11)
    - Chaney, Henry Allen (Box 11)
    - Clayberg, George Manfred (Box 11)
    - Cocker, William Johnson (Box 11)
    - Cook, Samuel Fletcher (Box 11)
    - Crouse, Daniel Webster (Box 11)
    - Darby, William Johnson (Box 11)
    - Day, William Rufus (Box 11)
    - Dewey, Franklin Smith (Box 11)
    - Dickinson, Oliver Pantridge (Box 11)
    - Dudgedon, Frederick Anthony (Box 11)
    - Durkee, Henry Rogers (Box 11)
    - DuShane, James (Box 11)
    - Fearon, Robert R. Newton (Box 11)
      [107?]
    - Fleming, Edwin (Box 11)
    - Fox, Orson Oscar (Box 11)
    - Freeman, John Charles (Box 11)
    - Gelston, Joseph Mills (Box 11)
    - Gibson, William Jay (Box 11)
    - Grant, Emory Levi (Box 11)
    - Guthrie, Nathan Lewis (Box 11)
    - Hall, Stephen Cogswell (Box 11)
    - Hamilton, Charles Hadley (Box 11)
    - Hamilton, Francis Marion (Box 11)
    - Hamilton, Walter Monroe (Box 11)
    - Hamilton, Walter Monroe (Box 11)
      (as child)
    - Hayes, Samuel Jr. (Box 11)
    - Herdman, William James (Box 11)
    - Hill, Eben Leander (Box 11)
    - Hinman, John Eugene (Box 11)
    - Hitchcock, William Douglas (Box 11)
    - Holliday, James Campbell (Box 11)
    - Johns, William Corwin (Box 11)
    - Kellog, Marmaduke Burnell (Box 11)
      [53, 152, 153]
    - Kerr, Theodore Frelinghuysen (Box 11)
    - Kinter, Charles Jacob (Box 11)
    - Kirby, Henry Walter (Box 11)
    - Lake, George Burt (Box 11)
    - Lamm, Henry (Box 11)
    - LeFevre, Owen Edgar (Box 11)
      [109]
    - Lord, Henry William (Box 11)
    - Lothrop, Benjamin Lombard (Cook) (Box 11)
    - Maltman, John Scott (Box 11)
    - Noble, Alfred (Box 11)
    - Otis, Charles Eugene (Box 11)
    - Pattengill, Albert Henderson (?) (Box 11)
    - Perry, Thomas Osborne (Box 11)
    - Phillips, Horace (Box 11)
    - Quarles, Joseph Very Jr. (Box 11)
    - Rexfor, Dwight Carver (Box 11)
    - Rhodes, Daniel Harker (Box 11)
    - Robinson, Albert Alonzo (Box 11)
    - Seeley, Thomas Jennings (Box 11)
    - Snover, Horace Greeley (Box 11)
    - Stillwell, Giles Ely (Box 11)
    - Swift, Lucian Jr. (Box 11)
    - Taylor, Thomas Chalmers (Box 11)
    - Thayer, Rufus Hildreth (Box 11)
    - Treadwell, Elijah (Box 11)
    - Tweedy, James Fisher (Box 11)
    - Updegraff, Robert David (Box 11)
    - Voorheis, George Phileman (Box 11)
    - Vreeland, Oliver Simeon (Box 11)
      [68, 85, 86]
    - Warden, James, Avery Satterlee (Box 11)
    - Whiting, John (Box 11)
    - Whiting, John (Box 11)
    - Wilkinson, Alfred Ernest (Box 11)
    - Williams, Benezette (Box 11)
    - Woodworth, Charles (Box 11)
    - Unidentified (Box 11)
      [74, 80, 81-84, 92-96, 101, 103, 115-116, 119-121, 123-126-141, 143-144, 146-148, 150-152]
  - Buildings and Miscellaneous
    - Group photos, unidentified (Box 11)
      [151-174]
    - Campus Scenes (Box 11)
    - Statue (Box 11)
    - Observatory (Box 11)
    - Northwest Corner of Campus (Box 11)
    - Medical Building (Box 11)
    - Family(?) (Box 11)
    - Unidentified (Box 11)
      [175-183]
- 1869 Class Album (Box 11)
  (Album of Edward S. Snover)
  - 1869 Class Album (Box 12)
    (Most photographs are unidentified, though identification May be on the back of the photographs.)
- 1870 Class Album
  (Album of Aaron Perry)
  - Faculty
    - Haven, Erastus O. (Box 13)
    - Williams, George Palmer (Box 13)
    - Cocker, Benjamin F. (Box 13)
    - Frieze, Henry S. (Box 13)
    - Olney, Edward (Box 13)
    - Watson, James Craig (Box 13)
    - Adams, Henry Carter (Box 13)
    - Tyler, Mose Coit (Box 13)
    - D'Ooge, Martin Luther (Box 13)
    - Spence, Adam Knight (Box 13)
    - Wood, DeVolson (Box 13)
      [1]7
    - Winchell, Alexander (Box 13)
    - TenBrook, Andrew (Box 13)
    - A number of group photos are contained in the album (Box 13)
  - Group Photos
    - Class of 1870(?) (Box 13)
  - Students
    (contains biographical sketch with each photo)
    - Adams, Arthur C. (Box 13)
    - Baker, Marcus (Box 13)
    - Baldwin, John A. (Box 13)
    - Ballenger, Charles (Box 13)
    - Barlow, Henry H. (Box 13)
    - Bates, George W. (Box 13)
    - Beman, Wooster W. (Box 13)
    - Bird, Judson S. (Box 13)
    - Blackburn, Julius A. (Box 13)
    - Blanchard, James H. (Box 13)
    - Boss, Clarence M. (Box 13)
    - Bumpus, Patrick H. (Box 13)
    - Burton, Charles F. (Box 13)
    - Bush, Thomas H. (Box 13)
    - Campau, George T. (Box 13)
    - Campbell, Oscar J. (Box 13)
    - Carter, Charles S. (Box 13)
    - Christy, T. Chalmers (Box 13)
    - Cooley, Eugene F. (Box 13)
    - Culley, John L. (Box 13)
    - Davock, Harlow Palmer (Box 13)
    - Day, William R. (Box 13)
    - Dawson, George E. (Box 13)
    - Dodge, Charles K. (Box 13)
    - Edwards, Charles S. (Box 13)
    - Emerson, William T. (Box 13)
    - Errett, Russell (Box 13)
    - Fearon, Robert N. (Box 13)
  - Students
    - Finley, Achilles (Box 13)
    - Fleming, Edwin (Box 13)
    - Foster, Morris B. (Box 13)
    - French, George J. (Box 13)
    - Gilbert, Charles P. (Box 13)
    - Haven, Otis E. (Box 13)
    - Hayward, James A. (Box 13)
      [567]
    - Howe, Frank H. (Box 13)
    - Howland, John C. (Box 13)
    - Hyde, Washington (Box 13)
    - Johnson, John W. (Box 13)
    - Jones, Francis W. (Box 13)
    - Ketchum, Eugene (Box 13)
    - Kintner, Charles J. (Box 13)
    - LeFevre, Owen E. (Box 13)
    - Lovell, Vincent (Box 13)
    - Maltman, John S. (Box 13)
    - Marsh, Milo E. (Box 13)
    - Matthews, William F. (Box 13)
    - Meyendorff, Michael A. (Box 13)
    - Mickle, George W. (Box 13)
    - Moses, Bernard (Box 13)
    - Noble, Alfred (Box 13)
    - Olds, Clark (Box 13)
    - Penfield, William L (Box 13)
    - Pennington, Darius C. (Box 13)
    - Perry, Aaron (Box 13)
    - Ripley, Henry C. (Box 13)
    - Shock, Willian H. (Box 13)
    - Stevens, Walter B. (Box 13)
    - Stocking, Leonard E. (Box 13)
    - Swift, Lucius B. (Box 13)
    - Thayer, Rufus H. (Box 13)
    - Thomson, Alexander (Box 13)
    - Tweedy, James F. (Box 13)
    - Tindall, Orlando L. (Box 13)
    - Voorhies, Peter (Box 13)
    - Waters, William J. (Box 13)
    - Wattles, Oliver H. (Box 13)
    - Weisbrod, Albert W. (Box 13)
    - Wells, C.M. (Box 13)
    - Whitman, Charles P. (Box 13)
    - Winchell, S.R. (Box 13)
    - Willits, Warren C. (Box 13)
    - Wing, Charles G. (Box 13)
    - Wylie, Thomas (Box 13)
    - Unidentified (Box 13)
  - Building and Miscellaneous
    - Benjamin Franklin statue, gift of clss of 1870 (Box 13)
    - Haven Hall (Box 13)
- 1870 Class Album (copy 2)
  - Buildings and Miscellaneous (Box 45)
    - Boulder inscribed "Class of 1862" (Box 45)
    - Chemistry Laboratory (Box 45)
    - Diag (Box 45)
    - Haven Hall (Box 45)
    - Mason Hall (Box 45)
    - Medical Building (Box 45)
    - Methodist Episcopal Church (Box 45)
    - President's House (Box 45)
    - South College, Mason Hall, and Haven Hall, 2 photographs (Box 45)
    - Union School (Box 45)
    - Unidentified Buildings (Box 45)
  - Faculty
    - Adams, Henry Carter (Box 45)
    - Bennett, Henry D. (Box 45)
    - Campbell, James Valentine (Box 45)
    - Cocker, Benjamin F. (Box 45)
    - Cooley, Thomas McIntyre (Box 45)
    - Evans, Edward Payson (Box 45)
    - Frieze, Henry Simmons (Box 45)
    - Haven, Erastus O. (Box 45)
    - Merriman, George Benjamin (Box 45)
    - Olney, Edward (Box 45)
    - Prescott, Albert B. (Box 45)
    - Sager, Abram (Box 45)
    - Spence, Adam Knight (Box 45)
    - Tyler, Moses Coit (Box 45)
    - Walter, Edward Lorraine (Box 45)
    - Williams, George Palmer (Box 45)
    - Winchell, Alexander (Box 45)
    - Wood, DeVolson (Box 45)
  - Group Photos
    - Faculty (Box 45)
    - Students (Box 45)
  - Staff
    - Jimmy, the janitor (Box 45)
    - Robert, the janitor (Box 45)
  - Students
    - Adams, Arthur C. (Box 45)
    - Baker, Marcus (Box 45)
    - Baldwin, John A. (Box 45)
    - Ballenger, Charles (Box 45)
    - Barlow, Henry H. (Box 45)
    - Bates, George W. (Box 45)
    - Beman, Wooster W. (Box 45)
    - Bird, Judson S. (Box 45)
    - Blackburn, Julius A. (Box 45)
    - Blanchard, James (Box 45)
    - Bradley, Franklin (Box 45)
    - Bumpus, Patrick H. (Box 45)
    - Burton, Charles F. (Box 45)
    - Bush, Thomas H. (Box 45)
    - Campau, George T. (Box 45)
    - Campbell, Oscar J. (Box 45)
    - Carter, Charles S. (Box 45)
    - Christie, Chalmers (Box 45)
    - Cooley, Eugene T. (Box 45)
    - Culley, John L. (Box 45)
    - Davock, Harlow P. (Box 45)
    - Dawson, George E. (Box 45)
    - Day, William R. (Box 45)
    - Dodge, Charles K. (Box 45)
    - Edwards, Charles S. (Box 45)
    - Emerson, William T. (Box 45)
    - Errett, Russell (Box 45)
    - Fearon, Robert N. (Box 45)
    - Ferguson, Luther E. (Box 45)
    - Finley, Achilles (Box 45)
    - Fleming, Edwin (Box 45)
    - Foster, Morris B. (Box 45)
    - French, George J. (Box 45)
    - Gilbert, Charles P. (Box 45)
    - Gilmore (Box 45)
      (first name unknown)
    - Haven, Otis E. (Box 45)
    - Hayward, James (Box 45)
    - Howe, Frank H. (Box 45)
    - Howland, John C. (Box 45)
    - Hyde, Washington (Box 45)
    - Johnson, John W. (Box 45)
    - Jones, Francis W. (Box 45)
    - Ketchum, Eugene (Box 45)
    - Kintner, Charles J. (Box 45)
    - LeFevre, Owen E. (Box 45)
    - Lovell, Vincent S. (Box 45)
    - Maltman, John S. (Box 45)
    - Marsh, Milo E., 2 photographs (Box 45)
    - Mathews, William F. (Box 45)
    - Meyendorf, Michael (Box 45)
    - Moses, Bernard (Box 45)
    - Noble, Alfred (Box 45)
    - Olds, Clark (Box 45)
    - Penfield, William L. (Box 45)
    - Pennington, Darius C. (Box 45)
    - Perry, Aaron (Box 45)
    - Price, Samuel B. (Box 45)
    - Ripley, Henry C. (Box 45)
    - Schock, William H. (Box 45)
    - Stevens, Walter B. (Box 45)
    - Stocking, Leonard E. (Box 45)
    - Swift, Lucius B. (Box 45)
    - Thayer, Rufus H. (Box 45)
    - Thompson, Alex (Box 45)
    - Tindall, Orlando L. (Box 45)
    - Tweedy, James F. (Box 45)
    - Voorheis, Peter (Box 45)
    - Waters, William (Box 45)
    - Wattles, Oliver H. (Box 45)
    - Weisbrod, Albert W. (Box 45)
    - Whitman, Charles (Box 45)
    - Willits, Warren C. (Box 45)
    - Winchell, S. R. (Box 45)
    - Wing, Charles G. (Box 45)
- Class Album 1871 College of Literature and Arts
  (Album of P.R. Flitcraft)
  - Views in Ann Arbor, Michigan
    - Huron Street (Box 14)
    - Union School Building (Box 14)
    - Methodist Episcopal Church (Box 14)
  - College Views
    - College Campus-General View (Box 14)
    - Law, Museum and Literary Buildings (Box 14)
    - Law Building (Box 14)
    - Museum (Box 14)
    - Statue of Franklin (Box 14)
    - Library Building (Box 14)
    - Medical Building (Box 14)
    - Laboratory (Box 14)
    - Observatory (Box 14)
    - President's Dwelling (Box 14)
    - Interior View of Adelphi Hall (Box 14)
  - Statuary in Museum
    - "Nydia, the Blind Girl," by Rogers (Box 14)
    - Ruth, the Gleaner," by Rogers (Box 14)
  - College Employees
    - Jimmie, the Mail Carrier (Box 14)
    - Robert, the janitor (Box 14)
  - Faculty
    - J. B. Angell, LL. D., President (Box 14)
    - E. Haven, LL. D., ex-President (Box 14)
      [0]
    - G. P. Williams, Professor of Physics (Box 14)
    - H. S. Frieze, Professor of Latin (Box 14)
    - B. F. Cocker, LL. D., Professor Mental and Moral Philosophy (Box 14)
    - A.K. Winchell, Professor of Geology (Box 14)
    - E. Olney, Professor of Mathematics (Box 14)
    - D. V. Wood, Professor of Engineering (Box 14)
    - M. L. D'Ooge, Prof. Greek Language and Literature (Box 14)
    - G. B. Merriman, Assistant Professor of Mathematics (Box 14)
    - C. K. Adams, Professor of History (Box 14)
    - A. K. Spence, Assistant Professor of French (Box 14)
    - W. W. Harrington, Instructor in Mathematics (Box 14)
    - G. S. Morris, Professor of Modern Languages and Literature (Box 14)
    - J. F. Billard, Instructor in French (Box 14)
    - E. L. Walter, Instructor in Latin (Box 14)
    - E Jones, Affing Professor of Greek in 1870 (Box 14)
    - A. H. Pattcngill, Assistant Professor of French (Box 14)
    - M. Woodruff, Instructor in Surveying (Box 14)
    - A. B. Prescott, Instructor in Chemistry (Box 14)
    - Judge J. V. Campbell, Professor of Law (Box 14)
    - Andrew Ten Brook, Librarian (Box 14)
    - Faculty in a Group (Box 14)
  - Students-Bachelor of Arts
    - Adams, Edward Mills (Box 14)
    - Bissell, Jonathan Edward (Box 14)
    - Chandler, Charles (Box 14)
    - Conley, Charles Edgar (Box 14)
    - Eastwood, John Foster (Box 14)
    - Flitcraft, P. R. (Box 14)
    - Fox, George (Box 14)
    - Goodell, Henry Martyn (Box 14)
    - Granger, Henry Chapin (Box 14)
    - Hamilton, Alexander White (Box 14)
    - Harsha, Walter Sutherland (Box 14)
    - Hudson, Preston Crane (Box 14)
    - Hudson, Richard (Box 14)
    - Knight, Earl Johnson (Box 14)
    - Latson, Morton Wilkinson (Box 14)
    - Mark, Edward Laurens (Box 14)
    - Mercer, Joseph Aaron (Box 14)
    - Millerd, Watson Birchard (Box 14)
    - Montrose, Henry Watson (Box 14)
    - Otis, Arthur Gray (Box 14)
    - Phillips, Horace (Box 14)
    - Phinney, Rufus Emerson (Box 14)
    - Preston, Benjamin Thomas Kent (Box 14)
    - Randall, Perry Anthony (Box 14)
    - Remick, Frank (Box 14)
    - Rice, Benjamin Greenville (Box 14)
    - Ritter, William Francis McKnight (Box 14)
    - Sleeper, John (Box 14)
    - Seavey, Gideon Webster (Box 14)
    - Warden, John Avery Satterlee (Box 14)
    - Wilson, Floyd Baker (Box 14)
    - Willett, Charles Joseph (Box 14)
    - Wright, Robert Mullins (Box 14)
  - Students-Bachelors of Philosophy
    - Avery, Elroy McKendree (Box 14)
    - Felch, Theodore Alpheus (Box 14)
    - Gillespie, Joshua Lathrop (Box 14)
    - Gorton, Charles Eugene (Box 14)
    - Hutchins, Harry Burns (Box 14)
    - Merrill, William (Box 14)
  - Students-Bachelors of Science.
    - Chambers, John (Box 14)
    - Cornell, John Patterson (Box 14)
    - Edgerton, Addison Joseph (Box 14)
    - Green, Samuel Sharpless (Box 14)
    - Rust, Charles Amasa (Box 14)
    - Sumner, Edward Blake (Box 14)
    - Wilkinson, Charles Melvin (Box 14)
    - Wilcox, Harry Cole (Box 14)
  - Students-Civil Engineers
    - Baldwin, Albert Evaston (Box 14)
    - Burr, James Dewey (Box 14)
    - Eisenmann, John (Box 14)
    - Fulton, John Addison (Box 14)
    - Littlefield, Josiah Loomis (Box 14)
    - Mason, Lyman (Box 14)
    - Parsall, Adrian Jefferson (Box 14)
    - Pennington, Baron Humboldt (Box 14)
    - Perry, Elliott Davis (Box 14)
    - Pratt, Charles (Box 14)
    - Raymond, Alexander Bunker (Box 14)
    - Smith, Curtis Culross (Box 14)
      [00]
    - Walker, Samuel Wolcott (Box 14)
    - Webb, John Burkitt (Box 14)
    - Class in Group (Box 14)
- 1871 Class Album
  (Album of A.J. Parshall)
  - 1871 Class Album (Box 15)
    (Photos are not identified, 84 photos. Includes many of the photos in the album in box 17 though not in the same order)
- 1871 Class Album (Literary and Engineering)
  - Buildings and Miscellaneous
    - Class Banner (Box 16)
    - Unidentified group of students (Box 16)
    - Unidentified group of faculty (Box 16)
    - Unidentified group (Box 16)
    - General view of campus (Box 16)
    - Law College (Box 16)
    - Walk to South College (Box 16)
    - Law College and statue (Box 16)
    - University Building (Box 16)
    - University Building (Box 16)
    - Chemical Laboratory (Box 16)
    - Medical College (Box 16)
    - Detroit Observatory (Box 16)
  - Buildings and Miscellaneous
    - President's House (Box 16)
    - Walk toward Chemical Laboratory (Box 16)
    - Unidentified street (Box 16)
    - Interior of the library (Box 16)
    - Alpha Nu Hall (Box 16)
    - Alpha Nu Hall (Box 16)
    - Nydia (Box 16)
    - Ruth (Box 16)
  - Faculty
    - Angell, James B. (Box 16)
    - Haven, Erastus O. (Box 16)
    - Frieze, Henry S. (Box 16)
    - Williams, George P. (Box 16)
    - Winchell, Alexander (Box 16)
    - Wood, DeVolson (Box 16)
    - Campbell, James V. (Box 16)
    - Olney, Edward (Box 16)
    - Cocker, Benjamin F. (Box 16)
    - Tyler, Moses C. (Box 16)
    - D'Ooge, Martin (Box 16)
    - Adams, Charles K. (Box 16)
    - Prescott, Albert B. (Box 16)
    - Merriman, George B. (Box 16)
    - Morris, George S. (Box 16)
    - Jones, Elisha (Box 16)
    - Walter, Edward L. (Box 16)
    - Pattengill, Albert H. (Box 16)
    - Rose, Preston B. (Box 16)
    - Harrington, Mark W. (Box 16)
    - Maasbert, Augustus (Box 16)
    - Billard, Jules F. (Box 16)
    - Lawton, Charles D. (Box 16)
    - Davis, Raymond C. (Box 16)
    - Bennett, Henry D. (Box 16)
  - Students
    - Adams, Edward M. (Box 16)
    - Avery, Elroy M. (Box 16)
    - Baldwin, Albert F. (Box 16)
    - Vissell, Jonathan E. (Box 16)
    - Burr, James D. (Box 16)
    - Chambers, John D. (Box 16)
    - Chandler, Charles (Box 16)
    - Conley, Charles E. (Box 16)
    - Cornell, John P. (Box 16)
    - Eastwood, John F. (Box 16)
    - Edgerton, Addison J. (Box 16)
    - Eisenmann, John (Box 16)
    - Felch, Theodore A. (Box 16)
    - Flitcraft, Pembrook R. (Box 16)
    - Fox, George T. (Box 16)
    - Fulton, John A. (Box 16)
    - Gillespie, F. Lathrop (Box 16)